<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Glow Getter</string>
    <string name="tagline">Find Your Perfect Match</string>
    <string name="eyes">Eyes</string>
    <string name="face">Face</string>
    <string name="lips">Lips</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="categories">categories</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="guides">guides</string>
    <string name="eyebrow_pencils">Eyebrow Pencils</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="lip_gloss">Lip Gloss</string>
    <string name="lip_liner">Lip Liner</string>
    <string name="mascara">Mascara</string>
    <string name="eyeliner">Eyeliner</string>
    <string name="eyeshadow">Eyeshadow</string>
    <string name="foundation">Foundation</string>
    <string name="blush">Blush</string>
    <string name="bronzer">Bronzer</string>
    <string name="concealer">Concealer</string>
    <string name="contour">Contour</string>
    <string name="highlighter">Highlighter</string>
    <string name="lipstick">Lipstick</string>
    <string name="eyebrow_pencil_des">Eyebrows – the forgotten heroes of the face! But fear not, because eyebrow pencils are here to be your brow BFF. They\'re like tiny magic wands that can transform your arches from \"meh\" to \"wow.\"\n</string>
    <string name="mascara_des">Lashes so luscious, they\'ll make your eyes do the talking! Mascara is your secret weapon for taking your peepers from sleepy to stunning.</string>
    <string name="eyeliner_des">Eyeliner: it can be your secret weapon for bedroom eyes or a bold, dramatic look. But for beginners, it can also feel like trying to park a car with your eyes closed. Don\'t worry, we\'ve all been there! Pencils are recommended for beginners.</string>
    <string name="eyeshadow_des">Imagine your eyelids as a canvas, ready for a masterpiece. Eyeshadow lets you be the artist, with a million shades to play with! Want a subtle daytime look or a showstopping smoky eye? Eyeshadow unlocks endless possibilities. Dive in and discover your inner makeup maestro!</string>
    <string name="lip_gloss_des">Feeling like your lips need a little somethin\' somethin\'? Enter lip gloss, the magic potion for kissable shine! It\'s like giving your lips a glazed donut makeover – yummy and oh-so pretty.</string>
    <string name="lip_liner_des">Lip liner: it\'s not just for pros anymore! This handy tool is your BFF (besides lipstick, of course) for creating defined, kissable lips. Think of it like a sketch artist for your smile, helping you achieve perfect shape and preventing color from bleeding.</string>
    <string name="lipstick_des">It\'s more than just color, it\'s an attitude! From bold reds to playful pinks, lipstick lets you transform your look in a single swipe. It\'s like a magic wand for your lips, ready to unleash your inner confidence and turn up the volume on your smile.</string>
    <string name="foundation_des">Imagine your face as a blank canvas, waiting for your creativity to shine through. That\'s the magic of foundation! It helps even out your skin tone and creates a smooth base for the rest of your makeup routine. It\'s like hitting the \"refresh\" button for your complexion, giving you the perfect starting point to unleash your inner makeup artist.</string>
    <string name="blush_des">Feeling like your face is a little one-tone? Blush is here to add a pop of color and make your cheeks look like they just got a compliment (or maybe a little sun-kissed). It\'s like a magic wand for your face, bringing a rosy glow and a touch of life to your whole look.</string>
    <string name="bronzer_des">Bronzer is your key to unlocking a sculpted and radiant face. It adds warmth and dimension, highlighting your natural features for a stunning look. Think of it like your personal sunshine in a compact!</string>
    <string name="concealer_des">Feeling like those pesky blemishes or dark circles are stealing your spotlight? Concealer is here to save the day! It\'s like a magic wand for your face, helping to camouflage imperfections and brighten tired-looking eyes.</string>
    <string name="contour_des">Ever wonder how makeup artists achieve those chiseled cheekbones and defined jawlines? Contouring is their secret weapon (and now it can be yours too!). It\'s like a magic light and shadow kit for your face, helping you create depth and dimension for a more sculpted look.</string>
    <string name="highlighter_des">Highlighter is your key to unlocking that mythical radiance! It\'s like a magic potion for your face, adding a touch of shimmer and light that takes your makeup look from ordinary to extraordinary.</string>
    <string name="error">Error Loading Content</string>
    <string name="popular_products">Popular Products</string>
    <string name="liquid_foundation">Liquid Foundation</string>
    <string name="bb_cc_cream"><![CDATA[BB & CC Cream]]></string>
    <string name="mineral_foundation">Mineral Foundation</string>
    <string name="powder_foundation">Powder Foundation</string>
    <string name="powder_blush">Powder</string>
    <string name="cream_blush">Cream</string>
    <string name="guides_and_tutorials">Guides</string>
    <string name="glossary">Glossary</string>
    <string name="get_started">Go Find Your Glow!</string>
    <string name="continue_without_account">Continue Without Account</string>
    <string name="glossary_intro">Feeling lost in a land of brushes and powders? Don\'t worry, this glossary is your magic decoder ring for the world of makeup! Click on the buttons below to jump to each section.</string>
    <string name="glossary_top_app_bar">Makeup Glossary for Beginners</string>
    <string name="face_stuff">Face Stuff</string>
    <string name="lip_service">Lip Service</string>
    <string name="finishing_touches">Finishing Touches</string>
    <string name="eye_candy">Eye Candy</string>
    <string name="brush_buddies">Brush Buddies</string>
    <string name="bonus_words">Bonus Words</string>
    <string name="face_items_foundation">Foundation: Your skin\'s BFF, this evens out your tone and creates a flawless canvas (think of it as Instagram for your face, but in real life).</string>
    <string name="face_items_primer">Primer: Like double-sided tape for makeup, this helps everything stick and makes your masterpiece last longer.</string>
    <string name="face_items_concealer">Concealer: Your secret weapon against dark circles, blemishes, and anything else trying to steal your glow.</string>
    <string name="face_items_powder">Powder: This sets your foundation like a boss, keeping you shine-free and camera-ready.</string>
    <string name="face_items_highlighter">Highlighter: Basically a tiny disco ball for your face, it catches light and makes your cheekbones, nose, and cupid\'s bow pop.</string>
    <string name="face_items_bronzer">Bronzer: Think sunkissed skin without the sunburn! This adds warmth and can even be used to fake some sculpting (hello, cheekbones!).</string>
    <string name="face_items_blush">Blush: A rosy kiss of color for your cheeks, because who doesn\'t love a healthy flush?</string>
    <string name="face_items_contour">Contour: Contouring uses darker shades to define your facial features and create a more sculpted look.</string>
    <string name="eye_items_eyeshadow">Eyeshadow: Like painting for your eyelids, this comes in a million colors and finishes to create endless looks.</string>
    <string name="eye_items_eyeliner">Eyeliner: This bad boy defines your eyes, making them look bigger and brighter. Think of it as the eyeliner flick that completes your superhero persona.</string>
    <string name="eye_items_mascara">Mascara: Lashes on fleek? This lengthens, thickens, and darkens your lashes for a dramatic (or natural) eye look.</string>
    <string name="eye_items_brows">Brow Pomade/Pencil: Your brows are the frames for your face! This helps you fill them in and create the perfect shape.</string>
    <string name="eye_items_eyelash_curler">Eyelash Curler: This little tool gives your lashes a dramatic lift, making your eyes appear bigger and brighter.</string>
    <string name="lip_items_lipstick">Lipstick: The classic way to add a pop of color to your lips. It comes in every shade imaginable, so find your perfect pout!</string>
    <string name="lip_items_lip_gloss">Lip Gloss: Think of it as chapstick with a dazzling personality. It adds shine and dimension to your lips, making them look plumper and juicier.</string>
    <string name="lip_items_lipliner">Lip Liner: This defines the shape of your lips and helps prevent lipstick from bleeding. Think of it as a coloring book for your lips, keeping things neat and tidy.</string>
    <string name="brush_items_brushes">Makeup Brushes: Different brushes have different jobs! Some are for applying, some for blending, some for precise work. Think of them as your trusty paintbrushes for creating a masterpiece.</string>
    <string name="brush_items_sponge">Makeup Sponge: This bouncy little friend helps blend out liquid and cream products for a seamless, airbrushed finish.</string>
    <string name="finishing_items_matte">Matte: No shine, all business. Perfect for oily skin or a natural look.</string>
    <string name="finishing_items_dewy">Dewy: Think fresh, radiant skin! Like you just walked off a beach vacation.</string>
    <string name="finishing_items_satin">Satin: The best of both worlds! Subtle sheen for a glow without disco ball vibes.</string>
    <string name="bonus_items_dupe">Dupe: Not your BFF\'s actual lipstick (don\'t be weird!), but a more affordable product that\'s practically its twin. Score!</string>
    <string name="bonus_items_natural">Natural Makeup: No clown makeup here! This look enhances your natural beauty, like a subtle filter for real life.</string>
    <string name="bonus_items_full_coverage">Full Coverage: Need to hide the evidence of that late-night pizza party? This makeup completely covers imperfections for a flawless finish.</string>
    <string name="bonus_items_setting_spray">Setting Spray: The superhero cape for your makeup! This mist helps it stay put all day, so you can conquer the world without worrying about smudging.</string>
    <string name="guides_top_app_bar">Makeup Guides and Cheat Sheets</string>
    <string name="guides_intro">Feeling lost in a land of brushes and powders? Don\'t worry, these makeup guides and cheat sheets are your magic decoder ring for the world of makeup! Click on the buttons below to jump to each section.✨</string>
    <string name="brushes">Brushes</string>
    <string name="guides_brushes">Brushes got you feeling overwhelmed? Don\'t fret, makeup newbie! \n\nReal Techniques and EcoTools offer amazing quality at wallet-friendly prices. Want to level up your brush game? Morphe and e.l.f. have a vast selection for all your blending, buffing, and bronzing needs. Now go forth and conquer the makeup world, one fluffy brush at a time!</string>
    <string name="guides_eyeshadow1">Feeling lost in the land of eyeshadow, eyeliner, and brows? Don\'t sweat it, makeup newbie!</string>
    <string name="guides_eyeshadow2">Drugstore brands like Wet n Wild, Maybelline, and e.l.f. offer fantastic (and affordable!) options. We\'re talking pigmented eyeshadow palettes in every shade imaginable, smooth eyeliners for precise lines, and brow pencils or gels to tame those arches. Time to ditch the makeup struggle and create stunning eye looks that won\'t break the bank! \n\nIf you want to step up your makeup game, dive into the world of higher-end brands!  Sephora\'s got your back with cult-favorites like Urban Decay\'s Naked palettes (a must-have for any eyeshadow enthusiast) and Fenty Beauty\'s Fly Pencil eyeliner for effortless definition.  Ulta boasts Too Faced\'s Born This Way Super Brow for natural-looking brows and Tarte\'s Tartelette in Bloom Clay Eyeshadow Palette, packed with gorgeous, blendable shades.  \n\nGet ready to experience the luxurious quality and pigment payoff these brands offer, and watch your eye looks transform!</string>
    <string name="guides_lips1">Lip goals without breaking the bank? We got you!</string>
    <string name="guides_lips2">Drugstore darlings like NYX Professional Makeup offer a fantastic selection of lip products. NYX Slide On Lip Pencils line your lips with creamy color that stays put, while their Butter Gloss delivers a high-shine finish with a hint of color. Craving a liquid lipstick that won\'t dry out your lips? Milani\'s Matte Liquid Lipsticks come in a vast array of shades and offer impressive staying power at a budget-friendly price. For a universally flattering lip balm with a hint of tint, check out e.l.f. Cosmetics\' Tinted Lip Balm - it\'s perfect for everyday wear!  Get ready to rock luscious lips without sacrificing your savings!</string>
    <string name="contouring_and_highlighters">Contouring and Highlighters</string>
    <string name="guides_contouring_highlighting1">Wanna sculpt and glow like a celeb, but without the celeb budget? No problem!</string>
    <string name="guides_contouring_highlighting2">Drugstore Duos:  Wet n Wild\'s MegaGlo Contour Palette offers buildable shades for sculpting and highlighting, while Milani\'s Baked Multitasking Makeup Stick lets you contour and highlight on the go!\n\nMid-Range Marvels:  For a step up, e.l.f.\'s Putty Primer is a fantastic base for your contour and highlight, while Maybelline\'s Face Studio Master Contour Palette provides a range of blendable shades for a natural-looking definition.\n\nHigh-End Hues:  Ready to splurge?  Sephora\'s Fenty Beauty Match Stix Skinstick lets you customize your contour and highlight shades for a flawless finish, while NARS\' Radiant Creamy Concealer is a cult-favorite for brightening under eyes and highlighting cheekbones.</string>
    <string name="guides_foundation1">Face feeling bare? Foundation to the rescue!</string>
    <string name="guides_foundation2">Drugstore Deliverance: Maybelline\'s Fit Me Matte + Poreless Foundation offers lightweight, buildable coverage for oily and normal skin, while L\'Oreal\'s Infallible Pro-Matte Foundation tackles shine and provides full coverage for those who need it most.\n\nMid-Range Must-Haves:  For a dewy, radiant finish, e.l.f.\'s Flawless Finish Foundation is a steal, while NYX Professional Makeup\'s Born This Way Foundation offers medium, buildable coverage that feels like a second skin.\n\nHigh-End Holy Grails:  Sephora beckons with Fenty Beauty\'s Pro Filt\'r Soft Matte Longwear Foundation, a favorite for its long-lasting, weightless matte finish in a massive shade range.  Ulta boasts Lancôme\'s Teint Idole Ultra Long Wear Foundation, offering full coverage and a flawless finish that lasts all day.\n\nFind your perfect foundation match, no matter your skin type or budget, and get ready to rock a flawless base!</string>
</resources>