<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Glow Getter</string>
    <string name="tagline">Find Your Perfect Match</string>
    <string name="eyes">Eyes</string>
    <string name="face">Face</string>
    <string name="lips">Lips</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="categories">categories</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="guides">guides</string>
    <string name="find">Find</string>
    <string name="your_glow">Your Glow</string>
    <string name="eyebrow_pencils">Eyebrow Pencils</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter your name below</string>
    <string name="lip_gloss">Lip Gloss</string>
    <string name="lip_liner">Lip Liner</string>
    <string name="mascara">Mascara</string>
    <string name="eyeliner">Eyeliner</string>
    <string name="eyeshadow">Eyeshadow</string>
    <string name="foundation">Foundation</string>
    <string name="blush">Blush</string>
    <string name="bronzer">Bronzer</string>
    <string name="concealer">Concealer</string>
    <string name="contour">Contour</string>
    <string name="highlighter">Highlighter</string>
    <string name="lipstick">Lipstick</string>
    <string name="eyebrow_pencil_des">Eyebrows – the forgotten heroes of the face! But fear not, because eyebrow pencils are here to be your brow BFF. They\'re like tiny magic wands that can transform your arches from \"meh\" to \"wow.\"\n</string>
    <string name="mascara_des">Lashes so luscious, they\'ll make your eyes do the talking! Mascara is your secret weapon for taking your peepers from sleepy to stunning.</string>
    <string name="eyeliner_des">Eyeliner: it can be your secret weapon for bedroom eyes or a bold, dramatic look. But for beginners, it can also feel like trying to park a car with your eyes closed. Don\'t worry, we\'ve all been there! Pencils are recommended for beginners.</string>
    <string name="eyeshadow_des">Imagine your eyelids as a canvas, ready for a masterpiece. Eyeshadow lets you be the artist, with a million shades to play with! Want a subtle daytime look or a showstopping smoky eye? Eyeshadow unlocks endless possibilities. Dive in and discover your inner makeup maestro!</string>
    <string name="lip_gloss_des">Feeling like your lips need a little somethin\' somethin\'? Enter lip gloss, the magic potion for kissable shine! It\'s like giving your lips a glazed donut makeover – yummy and oh-so pretty.</string>
    <string name="lip_liner_des">Lip liner: it\'s not just for pros anymore! This handy tool is your BFF (besides lipstick, of course) for creating defined, kissable lips. Think of it like a sketch artist for your smile, helping you achieve perfect shape and preventing color from bleeding.</string>
    <string name="lipstick_des">It\'s more than just color, it\'s an attitude! From bold reds to playful pinks, lipstick lets you transform your look in a single swipe. It\'s like a magic wand for your lips, ready to unleash your inner confidence and turn up the volume on your smile.</string>
    <string name="foundation_des">Imagine your face as a blank canvas, waiting for your creativity to shine through. That\'s the magic of foundation! It helps even out your skin tone and creates a smooth base for the rest of your makeup routine. It\'s like hitting the \"refresh\" button for your complexion, giving you the perfect starting point to unleash your inner makeup artist.</string>
    <string name="blush_des">Feeling like your face is a little one-tone? Blush is here to add a pop of color and make your cheeks look like they just got a compliment (or maybe a little sun-kissed). It\'s like a magic wand for your face, bringing a rosy glow and a touch of life to your whole look.</string>
    <string name="bronzer_des">Bronzer is your key to unlocking a sculpted and radiant face. It adds warmth and dimension, highlighting your natural features for a stunning look. Think of it like your personal sunshine in a compact!</string>
    <string name="concealer_des">Feeling like those pesky blemishes or dark circles are stealing your spotlight? Concealer is here to save the day! It\'s like a magic wand for your face, helping to camouflage imperfections and brighten tired-looking eyes.</string>
    <string name="contour_des">Ever wonder how makeup artists achieve those chiseled cheekbones and defined jawlines? Contouring is their secret weapon (and now it can be yours too!). It\'s like a magic light and shadow kit for your face, helping you create depth and dimension for a more sculpted look.</string>
    <string name="highlighter_des">Highlighter is your key to unlocking that mythical radiance! It\'s like a magic potion for your face, adding a touch of shimmer and light that takes your makeup look from ordinary to extraordinary.</string>
    <string name="error">Error Loading Content</string>
    <string name="popular_products">Popular Products</string>
    <string name="liquid_foundation">Liquid Foundation</string>
    <string name="bb_cc_cream"><![CDATA[BB & CC Cream]]></string>
    <string name="mineral_foundation">Mineral Foundation</string>
    <string name="powder_foundation">Powder Foundation</string>
    <string name="powder_blush">Powder</string>
    <string name="cream_blush">Cream</string>
    <string name="store_locator">Store Locator</string>
    <string name="guides_and_tutorials">Guides</string>
    <string name="glossary">Glossary</string>
    <string name="get_started">Go Find Your Glow!</string>
</resources>